It's not every day that an actress admits to having a crush on a hero, and that too on national 
television. But Sara All Khan is unlike any. She is as unfiltered as it can get. On Koffee With Karan, she revealed that she finds Kartik Aaryan cute and would want to go out on a date with 
Karan, she revealed that she finds Kartik Aaryan cute and would want to go out on a date with 
him. Soon Kartik and Sara's "yet-to-start" love story became the talk of the town. But now the 
actress has promised that she would soon get over it.

Talking about her comment on having a crush on Kartik Aaryan, Sara in an interview to a 
magazine said, "If you knew all the thoughts I have but don't do anything about, I promise we 
would get over this Kartik Aaryan thing."

She added, "I don't think a boyfriend will mean the end of the world. I don't think that it's 
impossible to go out clubbing with your friends every once in a while."

It all began on Karan Johar's chat show wherein Sara admitted to having a crush on Kartik 
Aaryan. Since then, a lot has happened. Ranveer Singh introduced Sara and Kartik at an awards 
show, and then filmmaker Imtiaz All roped in them for his upcoming film. And very recently, the 
pictures of Kartik and Sara on a dinner date went viral.
